Oh, hey
You don't know, babe
When you hold me
And kiss me slowly
It's the sweetest thing
And it don't change
If I had it my way
You would know that you are
You're the coffee that I need in the morning
You're my sunshine in the rain when it's pouring
Won't you give yourself to me? Give it all, oh
I just wanna see
I just wanna see how beautiful you are
You know that I see it, I know you're a star
Where you go, I'll follow, no matter how far
If life is a movie, know you're the best part
oh-ooh
You're the best part
Best part
It's this sunrise
And those brown eyes, yes
You're the one that I desire
When we wake up
And then we make love (Make love)
It makes me feel so nice
You're my water when I'm stuck in the desert
You're the Tylenol I take when my head hurts
You're the sunshine on my life
I just wanna see how beautiful you are
You know that I see it, I know you're a star
Where you go, I'll follow, no matter how far
If life is a movie, then you're the best part
You're the best part, ooh
Best part
If you love me, won't you say something?
If you love me, won't you? Won't you?
If you love me, won't you? Love me, won't you?
If you love me, won't you say something?
If you love me, won't you?
If you love me, won't you? Love me, won't you?
If you love me, won't you say something?
If you love me, won't you?
If you love me, won't you? Love me, won't you?